

const KatakanaCards = [

    // Umlaut
  
  
      {
          id: 1,
          question: 'ア',
          answer: 'a',
      },
      {
          id: 2,
          question: 'イ',
          answer: 'i',
      },
      {
          id: 3,
          question: 'ウ',
          answer: 'u',
      },
      {
          id: 4,
          question: 'エ',
          answer: 'e',
      },
      {
          id: 5,
          question: 'オ',
          answer: 'o',
      },
    
          // K

      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'か',
        answer: 'ka',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'き',
        answer: 'ki',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'く',
        answer: 'ku',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'け',
        answer: 'ke',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'こ',
        answer: 'ko',
    },
   
      // K

      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'カ',
        answer: 'ka',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'キ',
        answer: 'ki',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'ク',
        answer: 'ku',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'ケ',
        answer: 'ke',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'コ',
        answer: 'ko',
    },
    

    // S

    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'サ',
        answer: 'sa',
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'シ',
        answer: 'shi',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'ス',
        answer: 'su',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'セ',
        answer: 'se',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'ソ',
        answer: 'so',
    },    

    // T

    {
        id: 1,
        question: "タ",
        answer: "ta",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'チ',
        answer: 'chi',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'ツ',
        answer: 'tsu',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'テ',
        answer: 'te',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'ト',
        answer: 'to',
    },

    // N

    {
        id: 1,
        question: "ナ",
        answer: "na",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'ニ',
        answer: 'ni',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'ヌ',
        answer: 'nu',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'ネ',
        answer: 'ne',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'ノ',
        answer: 'no',
    },


    // H

    {
        id: 1,
        question: "ハ",
        answer: "ha",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'ヒ',
        answer: 'hi',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'フ',
        answer: 'fu',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'ヘ',
        answer: 'he',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'ホ',
        answer: 'ho',
    },

    // M

    {
        id: 1,
        question: "マ",
        answer: "ma",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'ミ',
        answer: 'mi',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'ム',
        answer: 'mu',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'メ',
        answer: 'me',
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'モ',
        answer: 'mo',
    },

    // Y

    {
      id: 1,
      question: "や",
      answer: "ya",
  },
  {
      id: 2,
      question: 'を',
      answer: 'o',
  },
  {
      id: 3,
      question: 'ゆ',
      answer: 'yu',
  },
  {
      id: 4,
      question: 'わ',
      answer: 'wa',
  },
  {
      id: 5,
      question: 'よ',
      answer: 'yo',
  },  

    // R

    {
      id: 1,
      question: "ら",
      answer: "ra",
  },
  {
      id: 2,
      question: 'り',
      answer: 'ri',
  },
  {
      id: 3,
      question: 'る',
      answer: 'ru',
  },
  {
      id: 4,
      question: 'れ',
      answer: 'ri',
  },
  {
      id: 5,
      question: 'ろ',
      answer: 'ro',
  },

  // Y

{
    id: 1,
    question: "ヤ",
    answer: "ya",
},
{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ン',
    answer: 'n',
},
{
    id: 3,
    question: 'ユ',
    answer: 'yu',
},
{
    id: 4,
    question: 'ワ',
    answer: 'wa',
},
{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ヨ',
    answer: 'yo',
},  

  // R

  {
    id: 1,
    question: "ラ",
    answer: "ra",
},
{
    id: 2,
    question: 'リ',
    answer: 'ri',
},
{
    id: 3,
    question: 'ル',
    answer: 'ru',
},
{
    id: 4,
    question: 'レ',
    answer: 'ri',
},
{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ロ',
    answer: 'ro',
},


//////////// Stimmhaft////////

// g-line

{
    id: 1,
    question: 'ガ',
    answer: 'ga',
},

{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ギ',
    answer: 'gi',
},

{
    id: 3,
    question: 'グ',
    answer: 'gu',
},

{
    id: 4,
    question: 'ゲ',
    answer: 'ge',
},

{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ゴ',
    answer: 'go',
},

// z-line

{
    id: 1,
    question: 'ザ',
    answer: 'za',
},

{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ジ',
    answer: 'ji',
},

{
    id: 3,
    question: 'ズ',
    answer: 'zu',
},

{
    id: 4,
    question: 'ゼ',
    answer: 'ze',
},

{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ゾ',
    answer: 'zo',
},

// d-line

{
    id: 1,
    question: 'ダ',
    answer: 'da',
},

{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ヂ',
    answer: 'ji',
},

{
    id: 3,
    question: 'ヅ',
    answer: 'zu',
},

{
    id: 4,
    question: 'デ',
    answer: 'de',
},

{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ド',
    answer: 'do',
},

// b-line

{
    id: 1,
    question: 'バ',
    answer: 'ba',
},

{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ビ',
    answer: 'bi',
},

{
    id: 3,
    question: 'ブ',
    answer: 'bu',
},

{
    id: 4,
    question: 'ベ',
    answer: 'be',
},

{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ボ',
    answer: 'bo',
},

// p-line

{
    id: 1,
    question: 'パ',
    answer: 'pa',
},

{
    id: 2,
    question: 'ピ',
    answer: 'pi',
},

{
    id: 3,
    question: 'プ',
    answer: 'pu',
},

{
    id: 4,
    question: 'ペ',
    answer: 'pe',
},

{
    id: 5,
    question: 'ポ',
    answer: 'po',
},



    ]